The Search is On!
The Search for Santa Paws is a family, adventure film directed by Robert Vince.
When Santa and his new best friend, Paws, discover that the boys and girls of the world
have lost the spirit of the season, they take a trip to New York City.
But after Santa loses his memory, it's up to Paws, a faithful orphan named Quinn, her new
friend Will, and a wonderful group of magical talking dogs to save St.
Nick and show the world what Christmas is really all about.
Quinn, played by Kaitlyn Maher.
Willamina, played by Madison Pettis.
Paws (voice), played by Zachary Gordon.
Ms. Stout, played by Wendi McLendon-Covey.
Santa Claus, played by Richard Riehle.
James Huckle, played by John Ducey.
The Search for Santa Paws is a 2010 Christmas adventure
fantasy film released on November 23, 2010.
The title is the tenth film in the Air Bud franchise and is also a prequel to Santa
Buddies, as well as a spin-off from the Air Buddies film franchise.
The film explores themes of santa claus, dog, christmas.